<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>surface marking on ZDoc</title>
    <link>https://notes.zumafi.com/tags/surface-marking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in surface marking on ZDoc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://notes.zumafi.com/tags/surface-marking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Surface Marking &amp; Basics</title>
        <link>https://notes.zumafi.com/docs/ellisanatomy/upperlimb/surfacemarking/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://notes.zumafi.com/docs/ellisanatomy/upperlimb/surfacemarking/</guid>
        <description>Surface marking Bones and joints that can be palpated  Clavicle Supraclavicular nerves Scapula  Medial border Acromian process Coracoid process Scapular Spine   Head of the humerus at the apex of axilla. Elbow  Olecranon process Medial and lateral epicondyles Head of the radius   Ulna posterior border Wrist  Styloid process of radius Styloid process of ulnar Head of ulnar Dorsal tubercle of lister   Palm  Pisiform (FCU insertion point) Hook of hamate Scaphoid tubercle    Muscles and tendons that can be palpated  Anterior fold of axilla - Pactoralis major Posterior fold of axilla - Teres major, latissimus dorsi Medial axillary wall - Digitations of serratus anterior Radial border - Brachioradialis Radial pulse, FCR, PL, FDS, UA, FCU Anatomical snuff box - EPL, EPB and APL Extensor digitorum  Superficial Veins  Cephalic vein  Drains from dorsal venous network of the hand Origin posterior to styloid process of the radius, in superifical fascia Runs up the anterior aspect of the forearm, then lies in a grove along the lateral border of the biceps.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>